He's out and can't be stopped.
Escapee is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Campion Murphy.
While on a class observation trip at a local mental hospital, young psychology major Abby
Jones, has a chilling encounter with high-risk patient, Harmon Porter.
She returns home for an evening of normal study with her two
roommates unaware of the darkness she’s awakened within him.
Abby Jones, played by Christine Evangelista.
Jaxon, played by Dominic Purcell.
Officer Carter Thomas, played by Scott Elrod.
Lynn Peterson, played by Carly Chaikin.
Detective Alison Jensen, played by Faith Ford.
Renee Sanders, played by Melissa Ordway.
Escapee or Escapees may refer to:
A person who has escaped from imprisonment or confinement, particularly:
A fugitive
A person who has made a prison escape
A defector from an authoritarian
regime
"Escapee", a song from the 2011 Architecture in Helsinki album, Moment Bends
The Escapees, alternate title of the 1981 film, Les Paumées du Petit Matin
OnEscapee,  1997 action-adventure video game
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.